{
    "file": "Task-1",
    "questionCount": 10,
    "notice": null,
    "questions": [
        {
            "index": 1,
            "question": "What is the pin code of NMB",
            "answer": [
                "110023",
                "110021",
                "100001",
                "834008"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "index": 2,
            "question": "Name of the NMB's nearest Metro Station ?",
            "answer": [
                "Sir M. Vishveshwaraiah Station",
                "Dhaula Kuan",
                "Bhikaji Cama Place",
                "Delhi Cantt."
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "index": 3,
            "question": "Name of the bank whose ATM is located in NMB ?",
            "answer": [
                "Canara Bank",
                "Karnataka Bank",
                "Union Bank",
                "State Bank of India"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "index": 4,
            "question": "In which district of New Delhi does NMB lie in ?",
            "answer": [
                "South West Delhi",
                "South Delhi",
                "Delhi Central",
                "New Delhi"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "index": 5,
            "question": "Which organisaation has opened a store similar to Kendriya Bhandar in NMB clib house ?",
            "answer": [
                "NAFED",
                "Amul",
                "Mother Dairy",
                "7-Eleven"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "index": 6,
            "question": "Under which police station's jurisdiction does NMB lie in ?",
            "answer": [
                "a",
                "b",
                "c",
                "d"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "index": 7,
            "question": "Which Lok Sabha constituency does NMB lie in ?",
            "answer": [
                "South Delhi",
                "Chandni Chowk",
                "New Delhi",
                "West Delhi"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "index": 8,
            "question": "What is the name of the play school for kids in NMB campus ?",
            "answer": [
                "Bachpan",
                "Kidzee",
                "Montessori Learning School",
                "Wonderland"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "index": 9,
            "question": "Give the name of the college located next to NMB ?",
            "answer": [
                "Delhi College of Arts and Commerce",
                "All India Institute of Medical Sciences",
                "Jawaharlal Nehru University",
                "University of Delhi"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "index": 10,
            "question": "In which year did the house allotment begin in NMB ?",
            "answer": [
                "2011",
                "2010",
                "2012",
                "2013"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "index": 11,
            "question": "Something went Wrong! Oops",
            "answer": [],
            "correct": -1
        }
    ]
}